pngworkforce.com 2018-12-07

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

This Website collects Personal Data from its Users. The Personal Data is either collected automatically or provided voluntarily. Failure to provide the Personal Data may affect the use of the Site or the services offered. The purpose and methods of processing are set out below.

**1\. Information regarding Data Processing Ownership**

PNGworkForce.com is the Data Controller. 

Contact info:

PNGworkForce.com

PO Box 649

Gordons 

Port Moresby, N.C.D

Papua New Guinea

query@PNGworkForce.com

**2\. Data collected during navigation**

When you visit the PNGworkForce.com's Website, it collects certain Personal Data, such as the pages you view, the links or buttons that you click, the date and time when you access the Site, your IP address, your web browser and the operating system you use (the "Navigation Data").

The Navigation Data may, by its very nature, allow Users to be identified through processing and association with data held by third parties. However, PNGworkForce.com uses this data solely for the purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information concerning the use of the Site and for purposes strictly related to its operation. 

The PNGworkForce.com Cookie 

When you visit the site for the first time, PNGworkForce.com saves a Cookie on your browser (identified as JE). This is a text string consisting of a code stored on your computer. This code allows PNGworkForce.com to recognize your browser, to automatically identify you through your registered email and to display information connected with your interests. The Cookie is permanent and if not renewed will disappear after a period of 2 years. If you wish to delete the Cookie before this period, you can do so at any time using your browser settings. 

The Cookie will be placed on your computer only if this option is enabled on your browser. Some features of the Site may not work correctly if this option is disabled.

Third party cookies

PNGworkForce.com uses third party services that install Cookies. These third party services are:

\- Google Analytics, provided by Google Inc, which installs the Cookies "__utma", "__utmb" and similar. For more information: developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies

\- Google Adsense, provided by Google Inc, using the DoubleClick Cookie. For more information: www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ads/#toc-doubleclick

If you wish to receive further information about third party Cookies, please write to our email address.

Other Navigation Data

When you open a new Job Ad notification email or click on a link it contains, your action is tracked for statistical purposes.

**3\. Data provided voluntarily**

Your email address

PNGworkForce.com allows you to activate a notification system for new Job Ads (Job Alert). Users can activate the notifications using their email address, geographical area and/or the kind of job they would like to see Ads for. 

After your email address has been provided, the Data is used only to send an initial email that is just an example of the Job Alert service, and a second email as a reminder. Actual registration with the Job Alert service only takes place upon acceptance of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service by clicking on one of the links contained in the email.

The email address is stored for the period and the purposes strictly necessary to request consent, and the Job Alert service will not begin unless one of the links is clicked.

You can enter the email address manually or you can identify yourself through the social network Facebook authentication service provided by Facebook Inc. Facebook authentication allows access to some basic information on your profile and information related to the permission you give when you authorize our application. PNGworkForce.com, however, only uses your email address and does not record any other information, except in so far as is strictly necessary to make the integration work.

When you click on the links in the messages sent to your email address, PNGworkForce.com uses its Cookie to identify you on later visits, allowing you to change the search parameters you are monitoring and for which you are notified by email. If you don't want to be identified on the next visit, you can click on the "log out" link.

In addition to notifications for new listings, PNGworkForce.com can send you specific job offers. These offers come from our partners who are interested in the professional profiles you are monitoring. PNGworkForce.com will use the email address you provided solely and exclusively for the Job Alert service. PNGworkForce.com will not send any business or advertising mail of its own or from any third party to the address you give.

When you cancel the Job Alert notifications, the service will be discontinued and your address will be removed from our database. The service may also be stopped and your email may be removed from the database in other circumstances, e.g., when you stop clicking on the Job Alert links.

Users are free to give their own email address to receive the Job Alert service. Failure to provide it, however, will make it impossible to obtain the requested service.

Other Personal Data provided voluntarily

As part of the services offered by the Site, you may provide PNGworkForce.com with other Personal Data besides your email address in order to receive more information and services (such as requesting information, quotes, subscribing to services offered by the Site, replying to an ad, reporting malfunctions etc.). 

This data will be processed by PNGworkForce.com solely for purposes strictly related to your request. Failure to provide this information may make it impossible to obtain the requested service.

Ad reply form

This form allows you to contact the job advertiser directly, and also to attach your Curriculum Vitae. PNGworkForce.com does not store any of the Personal data provided in this way and only carries out the minimum processing of data necessary in order to send the advertisers the information provided. 

Job Advertisers

This part of the site allows businesses to request information on the services PNGworkForce.com offers for companies, such as posting job Ads on the Site. The Personal Data provided will be used for offers relating to the services mentioned, both through direct contact or by sending occasional email messages. 

Uploading a Curriculum Vitae

PNGworkForce.com lets you upload your Curriculum Vitae onto its system so that Users can access it at any time. 

Please do not include confidential data in your CV (especially concerning health matters, religious affiliation or political opinions). Should the Curriculum be examined, any such information will be immediately deleted if the written consent of the interested party has not been given.

**4\. Third party services**

PNGworkForce.com uses third party services for its statistics, for technical management and maintenance or to display advertisements on its Site. The list of services used, and thus the third parties, varies greatly depending on the national locations of the Site, making it technically impossible to list them in this document. We therefore suggest you contact us if you wish to receive complete information.

**5\. Personal Data Processing procedure**

We handle your data in accordance with legal requirements, taking all appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, unauthorized modification or destruction of Personal Data. The Data is processed using both manual methods and computers and/or telematic means, using organizational and logical methods strictly related to the stated purposes.

**6\. Place of Data processing**

The Personal Data is processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, but the services offered by Google or other partners, may be processed outside Italy and/or outside the European Union.

**7\. Data retention**

The data is processed for the time needed to perform the requested services and are deleted when the purpose for which they were collected and processed no longer exists.

**8\. User rights**

You may contact PNGworkForce.com at the contact addresses given, to obtain:

i. confirmation of the existence or otherwise of Personal Data regarding you and, if it is stored, the list of Personal Data in PNGworkForce.com's possession

ii. information on the terms and purposes of the processing of your Personal Data

iii. updating or modification of your Personal Data

iv. cancellation of your Personal Data, including the deactivation of the Job Alert Service.

**9\. Changes to these terms**

PNGworkForce.com reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, informing Users through the Site. Users who continue to use the Service after the publication of the new conditions accept the new Privacy Policy in its entirety.

**10\. Legal information**

This privacy policy is subject to the laws of Papua New Guinea.

**11\. Definitions**

Ad or Job Ad

A job advert accessible through the Site, whose content is published directly on PNGworkForce.com or retrieved automatically from other job ad sites, as indicated in the ad itself, and of which PNGworkForce.com publishes an extract. 

Advertiser

Those who publish Job Ads through the PNGworkForce.com website. 

Service

The service of indexing, publication, and displaying Ads on the Site and any communications via email provided by PNGworkForce.com.

Terms of Service or Terms

These general terms of service.

Personal Data 

Personal data is any information concerning a natural person, identified or identifiable, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

Interested party

The person or entity to whom the Personal Data refer.

Website or Site

PNGworkForce.com, a search engine for jobs that operates through local versions in various countries of the world, identified by the jobrapido.com website. 

Data Controller 

The natural person, legal person, public administration and any other organization or association with the right, also jointly with another owner, to make the decisions regarding the purposes and methods of processing of personal data and the means used, including the security profile, in relation to the operation and use of this Site.

User

The individual user of the services or products of the Site.
